-Yeah.
- They asked me,
were you two dating?
- Us two?
-Oh, my God.
I am engaged.
Babe, if you're watching this,
I am not in a relationship
with Sierra on Survivor.
Previously on Survivor...
Kyle wanted me out.
I am gonna get revenge.
"Congratulations."
This is exactly
what I needed, baby.
I feel like
I'm running this game right now.
I feel a close
personal connection with Aysha.
But if Aysha won't
work with me,
is it worth
keeping her in this game?
If anybody has an advantage
or an idol
and you want to play it...
One second, Jeff.
I was able to get an idol
that's good
for one Tribal Council,
so I'm gonna use it now.
First vote: Sol.
Third person voted out
of Survivor 47:
Aysha.
The tribe has spoken.
Sol...
Yes?
You got anything to say
right off the bat?
I'm glad I'm still here,
but, uh, yeah,
I mean, you guys got me.
Well played.
At Tribal Council tonight,
my ass got blindsided.
And the people who I thought
were my allies,
Kish and Teeny,
they went against
what I thought was gonna happen.
And Rome is still here.
That's what
I'm more upset about.
We know who Rome is.
We know what kind of guy he is.
-I know you voted for me.
- Yep.
And, uh...
It was part of the plan--
what I thought was the plan.
And you voted for me?
No.
-Who voted for me?
- We'll talk.
I'm at the bottom of my tribe.
I have to quickly get over it,
and I have to get my mind right.
Otherwise, I'm going home.
- I just want to say I'm sorry...
- Okay.
...because I voted for you,
and I need to explain that.
- You voted for me?
- Yes.
Okay.
And I know that goes against
every promise I made to you,
and I understand
if you're pissed.
I'd love to claim
the vote for Sol
as purely this mastermind
strategic plan,
but that's not entirely true.
I could not fathom
writing Aysha's name down
because of
my emotional bond with her.
You know, this isn't a moment
where I'm like, "Yes,
we just nailed a blindside."
It's a moment where I am upset.
I-I think that's gonna haunt me.
I think that's gonna be, like...
This is a game.
And if the people playing
the game can't handle that,
that's on them. It's not on you.
- Okay?
- I know, but, like,
am I the person
who can't handle it is really...
You're gonna be able to...
I wanted to come out here
and be this villainous
mastermind player
who was able to make decisions
based purely off
how I could advance in the game.
But at the same time,
I know myself.
I'm sensitive.
And that's something that
I just have to learn to balance
as I move forward in this game.
No.
That's why I was very-- I was,
like, I thought it was you.
I feel like
we all played that perfectly.
And now we have
the majority alliance.
We got a solidified alliance.
Like, we're,
we're ready to roll.
Tonight, Tribal Council went
exactly how I wanted it to go.
Aysha went home.
- Sol messed up,
and he knows he's on the bottom.
And Rome ended up prevailing, baby.
We all made it
through our first Tribal.
-Yeah.
-Mm-hmm.
- That's huge.
Yeah.
Which, like...
Oh, my God.
Yeah.
This Survivor game is going
perfectly for me
up to this point.
I feel like
I'm in control all the way.
So if we got to go
back to Tribal Council again,
I am 110% confident
it's gonna be Sol.
♪ Yeah, off the top, and
you know the bars are silly ♪
♪ Comin' for the money ♪
♪ And I'm about
to make a milli on Survivor ♪
♪ Yeah, with the Gata ♪
♪ Yeah, you know,
I'm coming so hot and I wanna ♪
♪ And I hope you listening ♪
♪ Got to clean it up
like I got some Listerine ♪
♪ I come hard,
everybody know it ♪
♪ When I come through,
I don't even show it ♪
♪ 'Cause we go to the challenge,
and you know we gonna win ♪
♪ Again and again ♪
♪ And Jeff says, "Get it on" ♪
♪ We gon' get it on ♪
♪ Everybody knows
when we do that this was on.♪
Ah, damn. That was a bad one.
- That was a bad one...
- No, that was so good!
Freestyling,
going with the flow
is kind of
how I'm playing Survivor.
And right now
Sierra is my number one.
The two of us
are sitting in the middle.
So if we go to Tribal Council,
we can stick
with Anika and Rachel
or pick up Andy,
and we still have the majority.
So we're in the know
and in the middle
and in the driver's seat.
- You feeling okay?
- I'm feeling good.
All right, good.
Yeah.
No.
I don't think it's a big factor.
- I don't think...
- And I don't think,
I don't think
it was something Ani needed
to come back and, like, plot
into our heads, too, but...
we need to make sure
we clear that air.
For sure.
Because that will change
my whole game.
When Anika
came back from the journey,
she said
the other tribes are picking up
that Sam and I
are working together.
We're not dating,
but we are working together.
And what
is giving them that vibe?
I'm not sure.
You've spent so much alone time
with Ani and Rachel,
- it's, like, equal. Like,
why is it that we're dating?
- I know, I know.
- Why couldn't you be
dating Ani or Rachel?
- Ani says it's aesthetic.
- She said,
it's Ken and Barbie, and...
- Ken and Barbie?
Get out of here.
Whatever. I'm not even
gonna let it get in my head.
But I think,
moving forward in the game,
I don't
want them to know that Sam and I
are this tight alliance.
So I'm gonna make sure
Anika and Rachel know
that I want to work with them
and make sure
that line is, like, clear.
Oh, are we alone?
- Yeah.
What do you--
How do you like, uh...
What did I say?
The... the Breadwinners.
Oh, oh, oh, the Breadwinners.
The Breadwinners? Yes. Yes.
- We are. We're the Breadwinners.
- Right?
- And we're gonna win that bread.
When it comes
to camp life and challenges,
the three girls here
have truly been
the powerhouses of this tribe.
And so we call ourselves
the Breadwinner alliance.
We have a very, like...
...relationship.
I just want to make sure,
at least going
into everything, it's us three.
- 100%.
- Oh, my God. Dude. Sierra.
- Let them see.
- Look me in the eye.
Look me in the eye.
- Absolutely.
-Yes.
- Okay.
Having a strong alliance
of women is incredible.
Anika has been
my number one since day one.
And then also having Sierra,
who I also really trust
at this point,
is amazing for me.
Breadwinners.
- Breadwinners?
I feel good.
I feel like my game's
going as well as I could hope
it could be going right now.
Sue?
-You okay?
What happened?
Just feeling emotional.
I just, um...
I'm feeling like
I'm tired, you know?
Like, when I get tired,
I just get emotional.
I don't want to be crying on TV.
Join the club. I already did.
Had myself a little cry
- earlier this morning.
-You did?
Yep. Once you accept
that it's part of the process,
it's a little bit easier
to let out.
Before I even
came into this game,
my number one target for an ally
was gonna be
an older woman,
preferably a mother.
I wanted to play with a Sue,
and the island fortune
brought me a Sue.
- Feeling a little better?
- Yeah.
- Give me a hug.
- Thank you.
- You know I got you, right?
- I know you do. Thank you.
I think she's somebody
who really wears her heart
on her sleeve, but
she also tells me everything.
- I'll protect you.
- Yeah, and I'll protect you.
- 100%.
- Yeah.
Sue has given me
every piece of knowledge
that she has in this game,
so I'm very confident in
my alliance with Sue right now.
-You should be
proud of yourself.
-Thank you.
Yeah, I know.
I know. I cannot wait.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, true.
Right now, people see me
as a mom. I'm a grandma.
100%, they're underestimating me
because I am
the older generation,
but I'm hiding
a lot from my tribe.
They have no clue
that I'm 58 years old.
-Damn. Really?
- Yeah.
Like, that's awesome.
That, like...
If the good Lord's willing,
that leaves a lot of time.
I don't need to be wheelchaired
around or need a cane or need...
- No.
- You know,
I can just do it all, so...
They have no idea
that I am a badass pilot,
and I'm an adrenaline junkie
always looking for a rush.
I'm here for the journey.
I'm here for
the thrill of it.
And this is exciting because
nobody would ever suspect
that I've been spending my time
secretly looking for an idol.
I want that power.
I want that protection.
I want the thrill
of finding an idol.
Ah. Oh.
No way.
It is
a freaking Beware Advantage.
I couldn't open
that packet fast enough.
The map was giving me
very specific instructions.
Now I got to get this.
But if I don't find
that palm tree and get my idol,
I don't vote.
So it's behind the water well.
Going that direction.
The rope was hidden in vines.
But now that I knew
what I was looking for,
that rope stood out
like a sore thumb.
A bucket fractures,
and paint just bursts
all over the place.
And I see the idol there.
I have no idea
what I'm gonna do.
Obviously, I don't want
to get caught red-handed.
This is crazy.
It is horrifying
to see all of this paint.
It looks like
blood splattered everywhere.
And I need to cover my tracks
because I don't want anybody
knowing that I have an idol.
It is literally
like a crime scene,
that I was the murderer,
and now I'm trying
to cover my tracks.
I'm so desperate
to get rid of all the evidence,
knowing that the police
are coming any second.
I've got to cover up everything
so that nobody knows it's me.
I have paint on my legs.
It's on the water well.
And then, on top of that,
the trees had paint on them.
It's just out of control.
I'm gonna kill Jeff
for making this so hard.
It's taking me forever,
but I slowly see progress.
And finally,
I got rid of all the evidence.
Not one person will ever,
ever know I have
a hidden immunity idol.
I pulled it off.
Hey. How was your walk?
Yeah, I'm just chilling.
No, I'm good. I'm good.
I just wanted to chill
for a little while and just...
-Of course.
- I don't know.
Is your chin okay?
Yeah.
Did you fall?
- I was playing with the machete.
I'm good.
I just, it's okay.
Is that blood in your hair?
I'm okay. I didn't cut myself.
I-I just did something stupid.
I'm fine.
Caroline and I
found Sue with the machete.
There is blood all over
her hands and all over her face.
Immediately,
my red flag was raised
because I was
kind of confused as to what
she could have possibly done.
I'm fine, but I just...
I have to clean up.
I'm a little mess.
-That's okay.
- But I'll talk
to you guys later.
Take your time. We'll probably
- be down at the beach,
uh, crabbing.
- Okay.
- Okay. Thank you.
-Yeah.
Oh, my God.
I got to keep an eye
on Sue.
I'm suspicious.
I can smell BS from afar.
Shoot, shoot, shoot.
Last night, I played my idol
that was good for one Tribal.
Usually,
that idol gets replaced.
-This is tough.
- Yeah.
You know, I know that
I'm probably the best one
at looking for idols
on my tribe,
which is a comforting thing,
but everyone right now
is looking for idols.
No.
Sol is looking hard
for this idol,
and that is very scary.
We want to make sure that,
no matter what, Sol cannot find
this idol.
Anyone but Sol. Anyone but Sol.
If you're gonna
keep looking for one, that's...
Yeah, that's more
of a threat than someone
just sitting back at camp
trying to be kumbaya.
Really, dude?
I know what he's doing.
He wants to vote me out,
and he's trying to prevent me
from searching for idols
so I don't get one.
And he's threatening me
to do that.
I'm just saying,
there's a time to do it
and there's a time not to.
And, like,
the people at the top,
they kind of have
that freedom to do it.
But, like, I don't know
why you would just increase
the target on your back.
He's, like,
ten years younger than me,
and he's talking to me
like I'm a kid.
What the hell? What?
What's happening right now?
And again, I got to go Zen.
"Sol, relax."
I don't want him
looking for an idol at all.
That's gonna be a problem.
We're fine
if he doesn't find it.
-Yeah.
- Which, at this moment,
he hasn't.
Sol and Rome
are on opposite planets,
and that is a positive for me.
I'm not here to play safe.
I'm here to create some chaos,
which is why I've been pushing
for them to continue clashing,
so they will not work
with each other.
I think my strength
is getting to know people,
really understanding them,
and then being able
to beautifully manipulate them.
I've never been
a babysitter before.
Really?
-No.
- That was my first job.
Hey, we're going
looking for an idol, guys,
if you guys want to come.
I'm just going
to refill my water.
I am now going
to go get coconut after this.
With Rome, it's either his way
or "I'm gonna pout
like a five-year-old" way.
He's gonna throw
the biggest tantrum.
I ain't trying to deal
with that all day long.
'Cause it's exhausting
and it's messing
my game up.
Could I have
a minute alone, please?
- No. It's Survivor.
I don't have to.
- Seriously?
I'm-a follow you around.
Now, can I, can I sit over there
by the beach alone?
- Like...
- I'm-a sit right next to you.
That's fine.
All right. Whatever.
It is about as awkward
as awkward can be.
I know that Rome is just trying
to protect our four,
but, like,
he just plays the game
at an intensity level
that is not a match
with my own.
He's not looking
for anything right now.
And he's devoid
of any sort of concept
of what Sol might be feeling
as one, a player,
and two, you know, a grown man,
a human being on this Earth.
It's just a lot. So much.
Oh, I'm sorry, Sol.
It's all good.
That's really not how I,
personally, want to play.
- You're not out.
- All right.
- They can knock you down,
but they can't get you out.
- Right.
Yeah.
Of course I feel bad for Sol.
Rome is being rude,
and, you know,
Rome and I have a really good
relationship and are very close,
but it's also
a complicated relationship
for me to navigate because
he's such a big personality
and does rub people
the wrong way.
I think each
of our mistakes was getting
a little too locked in with what
we thought dynamics were
- and not being
fluid enough, you know?
- Yes.
Absolutely.
Please don't tell Rome
I'm saying this.
You and I, if you allow it,
- we are allies moving forward.
- I know. Yeah, yeah.
- No, no, no, no, no.
I'm dead serious. Yeah.
- I'm cool. I'm down. I'm down.
I'm actually getting
really excited right now.
Sol is on the outs
and is a free agent.
And I want to really
nurture that relationship,
because Rome has ruffled all
these feathers that it's like,
I can only
make the case for Rome
so many times before it ends up
being a case against me.
What?
Uh-oh.
Might be Andy's.
I feel like
his bag's always open.
Yeah, it's definitely
Andy's Shot in the Dark.
Oh, my God.
Andy, why are you so sloppy?
-Yeah, just put it
back where it was.
-Just drop it.
- Just drop it
where it was. Yeah.
-Just drop it. Yeah.
Sure enough, Andy--
the one guy who might
need his Shot in the Dark--
somehow allowed it
to just fumble out of his bag.
Your Shot in the Dark
fell out of your bag.
It's sitting on the sand,
under the shelter right now.
You're gonna have
to go into camp and get it.
- Yeah.
- But also, like, make a scene.
Right now I'm a little bit
of a mentor to Andy's game.
I'm just showing him
how to play subtle Survivor.
Do you mind if I nap?
No, go for it.
He just needs
a little guidance is all.
I think
we're still working on it.
Big work in progress, but...
he's a bit of
a clumsy player at times.
All right, all right, all right.
Andy's kind of
like Survivor George Costanza.
He can't get out of his own way.
I just tore my underwear.
On, like, a... Oh, my God.
Yeah.
It's, like, gaping right now.
Everything Andy does...
Whoo!
...he should do
the exact opposite
of whatever he thinks
is the right thing to do.
I'm just trying to make sure
that I'm always
one step ahead of him
and that he's always coming
back to me with the information.
As long as
he's doing that, like,
Andy can stay around,
in my book.
- Two minutes ago...
- Yeah?
...I looked in my bag, and...
...the Shot in the Dark
was gone again,
and I looked everywhere, and it
was just on the ground at camp.
- Dude.
- I'm like, "What?"
- So I put it in my sock
from here on out.
- Okay.
- I'm like,
"Don't make me have to..."
- Don't worry. Don't worry.
Andy is such a sloppy player.
I'm like, "Do I really
want to move forward with that?"
I know that Sam
wants to work with him,
but I'm still up in the air,
and it's driving me
freaking nuts.
I just feel like Ani and Rachel
are definitely, like, tight.
- You know,
I feel like we're a three.
- Mm-hmm. Yeah.
- Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
- But I feel like they're a two,
and...
- Yeah, they get pretty specific.
- Yeah.
Like, you know,
they call-- they have a name.
Like, we're
now the Breadwinners.
- The Breadwinners.
- Don't say that.
Um, but, you know,
so, yeah, there is, like,
a deep connection.
I made a point
and made a mission to build
a real good bond with Sierra,
and it's coming on strong.
Whenever I talk to you,
I just...
You feel better?
I could cry.
Like, I just love you.
Oh, good.
I know. I love you guys.
I love everybody, you know?
Because she gave me
that Breadwinners name,
I know she's with me,
because I know she's throwing
that alliance under the bus.
She's throwing it away.
And I believe,
truly, that she's down
to work with myself and Sam.
I feel like I can tell you
everything Sierra tells me.
- Yeah.
- So, and it's very good.
I had
the most amazing conversation
with her this morning.
She said not to say it
to anyone.
I asked her how specific
that these other
women get about,
like, what, their alliance.
She's like,
"Oh, they get specific.
We're called the Breadwinners."
- That's what they call it?
- Yeah.
If she's
telling us the name, then...
- we win.
- Wow.
The Breadwinners.
I haven't heard that before.
Sierra and I,
we're supposed to be
riding for each other,
no matter what.
Why are you not coming to me
with that kind of information?
- You're my number one, so
I'm gonna tell you everything.
- Yeah.
Andy tells me
that you told him about a...
alliance name
that the three girls have.
- Rachel said that she's
calling us the Breadwinners.
- Right.
- I didn't come up with it.
- I don't care.
- That's, like...
- I didn't come up with it.
You know that
that's not where I'm going.
- You know I have to play it off.
- I know, but if, you know,
if, like...
- Okay.
- No, but why didn't
you tell me that stuff?
I didn't say,
"Hey, girls, let's
be called the Breadwinners."
I didn't come up with that.
I'm going along with it
because I'm doing what
I think is best for my game.
Andy, right now, is...
He-he scares me. I don't...
Why?
I don't think
Andy's gonna be loyal to me.
But we don't
have to go with Andy yet.
If-if we're at four, we can
always go with one of the girls.
I don't know if that's
what makes sense for me either.
Sierra thinks
Andy needs to go at the next
Tribal Council, and, uh,
that ain't gonna work for me.
Keeping Andy is
absolutely essential to my game.
I don't see a world
where it's the four of us,
and the two of them
aren't wanting to get me out.
Yeah, but that's not
gonna happen because of me.
Sam and I are just completely
bumping heads right now.
We might need Survivor's
alliance therapy at this point
because we're just going
back and forth, and I'm like,
"This is too early in the game
to be bickering like
a freaking old married couple."
Come on in.
Tuku and Gata getting your first
look at the new Lavo tribe.
Aysha voted out...
-Wow.
- Oh.
...at the last Tribal Council.
Well, well, well.
All right, shall we get
to today's immunity challenge?
- All right.
First things first,
got to take back the idols.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
- Yes, sir.
Once again,
immunity is back up for grabs.
For today's challenge, you're
gonna roll a heavy metal cube
to help you retrieve two bags.
You'll use
the pieces inside the bags
to build a window frame
and then attempt to toss
sandbags through the frame,
onto a barrel.
If you knock the frame over,
you got to rebuild it
and try again.
Once you've
landed your sandbags,
you'll then dig up a key,
open a gate.
That'll get you to the finish,
where two tribe members
will work together to build
a brand-new
Survivor fire puzzle.
First two tribes to finish
win immunity.
Safe from the vote.
Nobody going home.
- You will live to see day nine.
In addition,
you're playing for a reward.
Yes, come on.
- Ladies and gents, let's go.
Do I hear chickens or something?
Or animals? I don't know.
I'm, like...
- Oh...
- Oh, my goodness.
First tribe to finish...
- Oh, my God.
Three egg-laying hens.
- Egg-laying hens.
- Ah.
Second tribe to finish...
...six eggs from
the three egg-laying hens.
- Oh, my God, man.
- Wow.
- Okay. All right. Okay.
-Last tribe to finish,
otherwise known as the losers,
got nothing for you but a date
with me at Tribal Council,
where somebody
will be the fourth person
voted out of Survivor 47.
And as a penalty for losing,
I will take your flint.
Lavo, you are working
to earn yours back.
All right, we have no sit-outs.
We are even.
Five across the board.
Give you a minute to strategize.
We'll get it on. Let's do it.
Let's get it on.
All right, here we go.
For immunity and reward.
Survivors ready?
Go!
First, you got
to move a very heavy cube.
It's gonna
take everything you got.
Push, push. Go, go.
Make sure you don't run
into somebody else with it,
'cause it will hurt.
-Ride the bounce.
Ride the bounce...
-We got it.
- Great job.
-Ride the bounce.
Ride the bounce.
Keep rolling.
Tuku doing a nice job.
Watch your feet.
You got to get
it underneath the first bag...
- ...so you can get somebody
up top to retrieve that bag.
-Go.
- Lavo doing a nice job.
They're under that first bag,
sorta.
-Nice, Rome.
Rome going up top
to unclip that first bag.
Gata's at the first bag.
Tuku still going.
Unclip. You don't need to untie.
Rome's got it for Lavo.
-Get up there.
-Anika going up
for Gata.
Kyle going up for Tuku.
Anika has the bag.
Kyle has the bag.
Once you get that bag, get down.
Do not dillydally.
You're taking too much time.
-Yep, you got it.
-Now you got to move it
to the other bag.
- Rome has it. Get down, Rome.
-Jump down. Jump down.
Yeah, Kyle.
Tuku has their second bag.
Drop it. Drop it.
-Gata has theirs.
-Sorry.
It's gonna be Sol and Kyle...
Go all the way up, Kyle.
- ...and Sam.
- Nice, Sol.
You've got to empty those bags.
-Doing amazing.
- You're gonna find two sandbags
and the pieces you need
to make this window frame
- that you're gonna
throw the sandbags through.
-Good job, Kyle.
-Great job.
-Kyle has
his pieces free.
Starts building the frame.
Sol has his pieces free.
That's the top.
-That goes on top.
-Go, Kyle.
Kyle can start for Tuku
with his first toss.
All right,
take your time, brother.
Take your time.
On and off. Another toss.
Just misses.
There you go, Sam.
Sam has all the pieces.
He can start building the frame.
- Kyle tosses.
No good.
Kyle,
that sandbag will not count.
It's got to be a clean toss.
You got it, Sol.
- Yeah!
-Sol with the first one.
- Sol with two in a row...
- This now, right?
- ...for Lavo.
Wow!
All right, pull the corners.
Two tosses. Sol landed 'em both.
- You're made for this, Sam.
-Here goes Sam.
- Sam sticks one.
- Nice.
There we go, Sam.
-Kyle sticks one.
- Sol gave Lavo a big lead.
Sam, you're good.
Let's go, Gata.
- You're good, Kyle.
-Beautiful.
Let's go, Tuku.
TIYANA
Sandbags, sandbags, sandbags.
Everybody working
on the sandbags now.
- You got to get all
the sandbags to your platform.
They are very heavy.
You cannot start digging
until you have all
your sandbags on your platform.
Lavo, you're good.
Start digging.
Let's go, guys. Come on.
-We're good.
- Jeff?
- You're good. You're good.
- Dig.
-Come on.
Let's go, let's go, let's go,
let's go.
Now all three tribes
are in this.
- Two hands.
-Now everybody's
digging.
Two hands.
Oh, I feel something.
Feel it.
- Yeah. Good job.
- Nice. Let's go, baby.
Lavo has their key.
Gata has their key.
- Tuku has their key.
- Pull it!
Pull it, pull it, pull it.
We are dead even right now...
Oh, there's multiple keys?
...as we head into the final
stage of this challenge.
Unlock it. Unlock it.
Unlock it. Yeah.
You're good, Lavo.
Lavo's through.
They can start
working on the puzzle.
- Gabe has it for Tuku.
- Yeah, go.
You can work on your puzzle,
Tuku.
Gata's through.
You can work on your puzzle.
-Okay, babe.
-All right,
here we go, baby.
-It's gonna be
Caroline and Gabe for Tuku.
-Let's go, guys.
Rome and Genevieve for Lavo.
Anika and Rachel for Gata.
Okay.
Day eight.
You want to get to day nine.
- It's right here.
-Oh, yeah, it is.
Yeah, it is.
Caroline gets
the first piece for Tuku.
-Nice.
Way to go, Rachel.
- Yes.
And Rachel with the first piece
for Gata.
- Rome's trying
to get the first piece.
- Right hand!
He's taking the throne position.
- He will be handed pieces
by Genevieve.
-I got this one.
Got it.
Yeah, Caroline!
- You got it?
-It is Gata and Tuku
- moving quickly.
- Yes. Good job, Ani.
-Yeah, that's it.
That's it.
- Move.
Rome still looking
for that first piece for Lavo.
It's either gonna be that
or something similar to that
on the left side.
That first piece gives you
an idea
of how these pieces go together.
Once you get it,
it gets a little easier.
Great job, Caroline.
Not... That is not it,
either side.
Once again on the puzzle,
it is Tuku
and Gata in a showdown.
- Thataway, Rach.
-It is Gata in the lead.
- I got it.
-Then Tuku.
-Beautiful, Caroline.
And then dead last,
without a single spark
of flame, it is Lavo.
We just need our first piece.
Nope, not it, Rome.
-There you go, girls.
-Great job, girls.
Gata continues
to expand on their lead.
Gata looking very good
right now.
- Got it.
-Another piece for Tuku.
Yes, Gabe.
-Same story at Lavo.
- Not it, Rome.
Now you start
to question, "What is wrong?"
Not it, Rome.
Why can I not
get a piece to fit?
That is not the piece, Rome.
Not even one piece.
- That's not it.
Meanwhile, Rachel and Anika
making it look easy.
You're doing so amazingly well.
Like assassins, piece by piece,
one after the other.
- Caroline
with another piece for Tuku.
- Great job, Caroline.
You guys want to switch roles?
There you go, girls.
- Way to go, guys. You killed it.
- Finish it off.
Gata down to their last piece.
-That is it.
What a calm finish.
- Great job.
Gata wins immunity
and the chickens for reward.
- We got chickens.
-We're now
looking for one more.
Very similar
to the last challenge
where Lavo was struggling to get
anything going on the puzzle.
That's not it, Rome.
Rome's plopped in front
of the puzzle
and has made no progress
with Genevieve.
Come on, Jeff.
One after another,
trying every piece.
Nothing is sticking.
No changes made.
No assessment,
reassessment, nothing.
Tuku getting closer.
Oh, my God. Kill me now.
Gabe leaving Caroline
to finish it for Tuku.
Oh, my God.
Lavo just gonna watch?
There it is.
Tuku wins immunity
and six eggs, sending Lavo
back to Tribal Council
for the second straight time,
where somebody will be
the fourth person
voted out of Survivor 47.
A rare, rare visual.
A puzzle that ended
the same way it started,
as if it never happened.
All right, Gata,
another convincing victory.
-Good job, guys.
- Good job.
-Once again,
immunity is yours.
Nobody going home,
no Tribal Council tonight.
In addition,
waiting for you back at camp--
three egg-laying hens.
Well done.
Tuku also finished.
- Wins immunity.
Once again, safe from the vote.
Waiting for you back at camp--
six eggs from those three
egg-laying hens.
All right,
before I send you off,
we have a journey.
Gata, you're in charge.
You're gonna send somebody
from each tribe.
It cannot be somebody
who's already been on a journey.
So first take a moment and tell
us who's going from your tribe.
- It's gonna be Andy.
All right, now,
who's gonna join Andy from Lavo?
Teeny.
All right, Andy,
who's gonna join you from Tuku?
- We're gonna pick Caroline.
-Caroline.
- All right.
-Okay, Andy,
Teeny, Caroline,
grab your stuff, head out.
You will return back
to your camp
- in time for Tribal Council.
- Bye, guys.
-Good luck. Good luck.
-All right,
Gata, Tuku, grab your stuff,
head back to camp.
No Tribal Council tonight.
Nobody going home.
Yes, sir.
All right, Lavo,
let's first just talk.
Rome and Genevieve,
describe that frustration
because it's very different
when you're out here.
I've never tried to do a puzzle
under these conditions
- and with that pressure.
-So, you know,
the two times I've been
at the end of a challenge,
I've been able to clutch it up.
So I felt confident
that I would be able
to, you know,
potentially do this.
And then, you know,
your family's gonna be
seeing you try to do a puzzle
and not be able
to get one piece,
and it's just...
it's just really embarrassing.
All right, Lavo,
Tribal Council tonight,
where somebody will be
the fourth person
voted out of Survivor 47.
As a penalty for losing,
I will keep your flint.
You'll have a chance to earn it
back at the next challenge.
All right, head out. See you
tonight at Tribal Council.
Losing today's challenge
and the way
we lost it really sucked.
While the other tribes
might be enjoying chickens
and having scrambled eggs,
we've got Tribal Council,
and we are going to be having
a straight-up scramble
to see who goes home, so...
not great. Not great.
Ah, it's so easy
when you're sitting at home,
but when you're out here
in Fiji,
it is a whole different game.
Think you could solve this
puzzle? Apply to be on Survivor.
- Four for five.
- Yes.
Four Ws.
Look, we have an egg in there!
Hello, are you the animals?
The idea of eating,
like, some juicy,
hot chicken right now
just makes me want
to just die in a pool of drool.
But there are politics involved
in whether
to kill
or not kill the chickens.
We do have to feed them
to keep 'em strong.
Is anybody opposed
to just eating them?
They can eat grass.
So I kind of...
I-I... I don't know.
I want eggs.
I'd rather keep getting meals
out of them.
- I think so, too.
- Yeah.
- And that's protein.
I do want to eat one
at one point.
There's a lot of meat there.
I cannot
kill the chickens.
Like, I can't do this.
Chickens are near and dear
to my heart.
We go to wineries
that have chickens.
I feed them,
I hold them, I pet them.
I love chickens.
- Oh!
- Oh, my God.
- Sounds like he's got to go.
No.
My first thought
when we win is, "Thank you!
Some food, some protein."
But Sierra doesn't want
to kill the chickens.
She wants to just wait around
and hope that there's gonna be
dozens and dozens of eggs
that hatch.
-Sam!
- What?
The chicken's out!
Grab the chicken!
I'm eight days without food.
I don't care anymore.
Just give me the green light,
and that chicken, uh, will...
You know,
it's going to the butcher shop.
Well, that was embarrassing.
That was very embarrassing.
- I think we just
collectively know...
-Yeah.
- ...we're not good...
- At puzzles.
...at those type...
those types of puzzles.
I put myself in the final
position to do the puzzle.
I definitely want
to be the person
that's in that clutch role.
Yeah, not getting one piece
was demoralizing.
Yeah.
And honestly, I was just
absolutely awful.
All right, well,
you guys ready to go wash off?
I don't know
if I'm gonna go in the water.
It's so chilly.
I don't think
I'm gonna go in the water.
Fortunately,
I have faith in the core four.
So even though Gata chose Teeny
to go on the journey,
in our heads
we already know the game plan.
It's gonna be Sol.
It's just
about how it goes down.
So we all know the plan.
It just sucks
that it had to happen now.
I feel like
I should at this point.
I still have the Steal a Vote
in my pocket,
so, if I feel like Sol might
play his Shot in the Dark,
guess what.
I can use the Steal a Vote
and make sure he can't play
his Shot in the Dark,
because you have to have a vote
in order
to play a Shot in the Dark.
I'd rather try and convince him
- of another plan
and at least see how he...
- If he bites?
Like, we can get a vibe
whether he believes it or not.
But the thing is, I don't want
to use this Steal a Vote,
because if we, as an alliance,
can keep this advantage,
then we'll be sitting really
pretty heading into the merge.
I do think
we can maybe give him a name
and make him feel comfortable.
Does Genevieve sound believable?
'Cause we could always push,
like, we need tribe strength.
We feel she's given the least.
That's probably
the most believable.
Rome proposes,
"Let's maybe try to see
"if we can comfort Sol
in this fake plan
that the vote is gonna be
on someone else."
And I was like,
"Maybe. What about Genevieve?
"You know,
strength is a big issue.
So what if we say Genevieve?"
Just 'cause
I do not want my name heard.
It hasn't been heard yet.
I don't want it out there.
Do you think there's any way
we could convince him
to give up his Shot in the Dark?
Be like, "I am taking your vote
if you don't vote with us."
- Yeah.
- And we can say
that it's gonna be Genevieve.
Like, I could just
straight-up threaten him.
I'd have no problem doing that.
Yeah. That works.
Anything that works.
I feel actually
pretty good about that.
It might be a little villainous.
You know,
I could strong-arm Sol tonight,
and little does he know
that he's gonna be
gone regardless.
But at the end of the day,
at least
I'll let him choose
how he goes out.
- What?
- Just-just wait, just...
I feel like if I give him
that ultimatum, I feel like
he might actually break.
It's more than likely
gonna be you tonight.
But hear me out. I'm willing
to work with you for this vote
to make it the way
that we want to.
The way that we'll be able
to do it is because
- I have a Steal a Vote.
- Dude.
I will use this Steal a Vote
on Genevieve tonight.
But the only way
that I'm doing that,
- and I'm letting you
know that...
- Yeah?
...is if you give me
your Shot in the Dark.
I'm letting you know,
if you don't
give me your Shot in the Dark,
I'm using the Steal a Vote
on you tonight, and then
you can't play
your Shot in the Dark anyway.
I'm letting you know that right
now, and you'll be going home.
- I have the advantage...
- What are you talking about, bro?
You're, like,
threatening me right now.
This isn't a threat. I'm just
letting you know the situation.
- Is this real life, bro?
- This is Survivor, bro.
I was like, "Bro, really?
It's like,
you can't be
threatening people."
But, you know,
the villain
on this season is Rome.
"Congratulations.
This advantage allows you
"to steal a vote
from another player
at Tribal Council." Blah-blah-
blah-blah-blah-blah-blah.
It's a slap in the face,
'cause, uh,
nobody,
especially of Rome's size,
has ever talked to me
the way he has,
and I don't plan on working
with him ever in this game.
And then here's the thing.
Here's the thing.
- How can I...?
- That's fine.
If you don't want to do it,
that's fine.
I'm using my Steal a Vote
on you tonight,
and you'll be going home.
I can't believe
you're doing this to me, dawg.
Down to the water.
- To what?
- The water.
-You just threatened me.
-That's not a threat.
It's an ultimatum.
That's not a threat.
- That's an ultimatum.
- Oh, okay.
- An ultimatum is not a threat.
- Okay. My bad.
My fault.
You know, the obvious vote is,
we vote for Sol,
and then, on the other hand,
you have Rome.
His thing is,
"It's my show.
You know, Lavo is Rome."
And I'm starting
to get sick of it.
He's playing chaotically.
That scares me.
You know, I can trust him now.
Can I trust him
in the future?
- Yeah.
- Even if he steals a vote,
- that's two votes on Sol.
- Yeah.
Even if Teeny loses her vote,
if us two vote Rome...
- And it's...
- Rome will die. He will die.
- I know.
- You're...
I can see you grinning.
- Bad boy. Bad boy.
- Ooh.
- Naughty, naughty.
I want to switch the vote
onto Rome because
I think
the true benefit of this is
Rome is super tight
with Genevieve.
Once Rome's gone,
that leaves Genevieve
in a really vulnerable position.
Okay.
Dude, I'm ready
to go to Tribal now.
If we get out Rome, and
we let Sol in, into the plan,
Sol now trusts me because
I have created the plan
to save him.
He is going
to be completely shocked.
If this happens,
this will feel so... good.
Okay.
- It's going to happen.
- Okay. Yeah.
This is one of the best feelings
in the world.
Rome is the vote.
He's going to have no clue.
I'm so happy.
At tonight's Tribal,
Rome will burn.
-We're here. Whoo!
-We're here. We're here.
-Finally.
-A lot to talk about,
- I think.
- Ah.
I think we have
a big gossip session
- ahead of us.
- Yes.
I did not want
to go on this journey.
I personally think that journeys
are a great opportunity
to switch up your luck
if you're on the bottom.
But if you're in
a pretty good position,
like me, this just puts
a bigger target on your back.
Well, can we take some time
to chat?
Yes, we can chat beforehand.
But here's the thing
with Survivor.
There's gonna be twists thrown
your way that you can't control.
And you know what? I'm going
to deal with those risks.
I'm gonna deal
with them head-on,
and I'm going
to make them advantages.
- There was a bros alliance
our first few days.
-Oh.
Is it still kind of bro-y?
In general,
vibes have completely shifted
is what I would say.
- I'm glad. I'm glad.
- Yes.
I'm in a position
of low information, I think.
So I feel like, you know,
- on the bottom.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
And if you want to know
where the crack is at Gata,
like, come find me at the merge.
I'm trying to massage my image.
I'm trying to do some PR, like,
that if I am someone
who feels like a social outcast
on my tribe, that is
the picture-perfect archetype
of someone
that players want to scoop up
at the merge, not target.
Sol and Rome have sort of,
like, this machismo-off,
- where, like, they're... Yeah.
- Interesting.
Like, they are
kind of like an ego battle.
So I feel like
it would be one of them tonight.
- Those are my guesses...
-Okay. Okay.
- ...based on last time.
-Again,
I get really good vibes
genuinely from the both of you.
- Seriously. No, this is real.
- I know.
- This is better than I, like,
felt so far. Yeah.
- Yeah.
No matter what,
good luck, you all.
- No hard feelings whatsoever.
- Okay.
Okay.
I feel like I'm next.
- Yeah.
- Would you volunteer?
Ours is looking
really, really shaky, genuinely,
about
where the pieces are going.
I mean, obviously,
I'm going tonight, right?
Yes. Yes.
Is-is there a consensus,
though-- Rome versus Sol?
No, but I feel like
I do kind of trust the people
I'm working with,
but, like, you guys do
have to understand,
like, I'm going,
- and neither of you are going.
- Understood.
Neither of them are budging.
My next Tribal Council is-is...
is now. You know,
I don't have much time to waste.
Like, you guys
at least have some time.
I don't want to lose my vote.
- I think... I'm sorry.
- I think I have to think
about it.
- We don't have much time.
- Let me just...
Can I just think real quick
about, like,
- the numbers real quick?
- Please.
- Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
I'm getting so nervous.
If no one volunteers
to give up their vote,
all three of us lose our vote
at the next Tribal.
It's the very,
very worst-case scenario.
Okay, you know what?
I'll do it.
- I love you. Okay. Perfect.
- Thank you.
- I'll do it.
I don't want
to look back on this
and feel like an idiot, but
whether it's Rome or it's Sol
going home tonight, I think
it could work without my vote.
All right, guys.
Oh.
And in that moment, I felt
I'm losing my vote either way.
I either get something
out of it, or I don't.
- Okay, I get it.
-And so
it's an idol no matter what.
It's an idol...
that we agree on.
Yes. That's better.
Okay, but, like, we can't use it
to be funky with each other.
It's different rules.
All we have to do. Like,
when we use it,
it will be all in agreement,
- and we'll be ready to go.
- To use as an idol.
Now, this is a new amulet.
This is not like amulets
we've seen in the past. The
rules are slightly different.
We can use this
to be a hidden immunity idol.
But in many ways
the inherent dilemma remains.
Is this an opportunity for peace
and collaboration,
or is it an opportunity
for warfare?
Andy!
- Story time.
Whoo!
Welcome home!
Oh, I can't wait.
Feels so good to be home.
Hello.
No one came to greet me?
All right, well, let me
just start off. I lost my vote.
That's horrible.
I've mourned, I've cried.
It's a new amulet
split between the three of us.
- Here he is.
- Oh.
Oh, my God. That is amazing.
I actually think this is
a huge key for us to...
-Agreed.
- We form a dominant alliance
at the merge.
Long story short,
I ended up with a friend for us.
Okay, here's how it works.
Different type of amulet.
If the three holders can agree
to play it, and it's an idol.
Uh-oh.
Yeah.
So I was like,
"I'll just lose it tonight.
"'Cause I'm gonna lose it
either way.
- Might as well get something
out of it."
- Mm-hmm.
We all got amulets.
- Ooh.
-They can only be used
- when all players are
on the same beach.
- Oh, okay.
- No.
- Okay.
Yeah. Mm-hmm.
Me and Genevieve
are voting Rome.
Yeah.
I definitely feel powerless
without a vote.
But I feel really lucky
to have found alliance partners
who are coming up with plans
without me even being there,
especially with my number one Kishan.
I'm proud of you guys
for coming up with this...
That was all Kish.
I just, like,
sat here and got told the plan.
It was amazing.
- Just, are you telling Sol?
- We told Sol.
- You did?
- He is totally game.
- So I can tell Sol, too?
- Yes.
- Like, you're in.
- Yeah.
- You're fully in.
- And I'm so happy.
- Me, too.
Sol is somebody
who I want to keep.
And if that means
that we get out Rome,
who is a bit of a nuisance
around camp,
who stresses us out
in the game a little bit,
then great.
It's a win-win.
The plan was,
that me and Kishan came up with,
was to tell Sol
that we're voting for Genevieve.
Interesting.
And whose suggestion was
- to throw Genevieve's name out?
- Uh, Kishan.
But I get why you wouldn't...
wouldn't like that, obviously.
- Yes. Yeah.
- Nobody likes
their name being...
being the, you know, the decoy,
but obviously we, like...
- 100%. 100%.
- Yeah, we're good to go.
So it wasn't, like,
a malice thing
- that Kishan threw your name
out there.
- No.
- Of course not.
- Like, I promise.
Does Genevieve sound believable?
I'm not here to play safe.
I'm here to create some chaos.
What about Genevieve?
You know,
strength is a big issue.
So what if we say Genevieve?
Once Rome's gone,
that leaves Genevieve
in a really vulnerable position.
Rome going home
is Kishan's plan.
And I am a bossy, type A woman,
and I don't want to just
be going along with plans,
especially if they're not
in my best interests.
Like, Rome is an asset
for me in this game.
And he's ruffling
people's feathers, but not mine.
He trusts me.
He will have my back.
I mean, as much
as anyone out here will.
And the biggest red flag
for me is,
Kishan doesn't hesitate to use
my name as the decoy vote,
which lets me know
he's not really intimidated
or respecting my game.
So maybe it's time
to stop going along
with Kishan's plan
and make Kishan the plan.
- What's up?
- I need to give you a heads-up,
- and I need to make it quick.
- Okay.
You're the plan tonight.
I'm 100% serious.
- So, does Teeny
know about this?
- Everyone knows about it.
All these brilliant plans
are his.
What do you want to do?
That's just so wild
that Kishan would
throw that out there.
Why would they want me out
if they know I'm going hard
for the alliance?
That's just so...
The second
that I heard Kishan might want
to put my name out there,
I was a little bit hurt because
I wanted to do everything
that I could
to make the alliance
as strong as possible.
And now, at this point,
I don't feel like I can trust
anyone in this game
but Genevieve.
Does Sol know about it?
My Steal a Vote
could be massive tonight.
Maybe we could
just get out Kishan.
Or I could block him completely
from being able to vote
and put two votes on Sol.
And just like that,
Sol will be going home.
I'm willing to do it
because guess what.
I already know
the guy doesn't like me.
This, uh, uh, crazy, toxic,
brother-like relationship
is a huge problem long-term.
- He put Rome up to it.
- Uh-huh.
And everyone is benefiting
from you two fighting.
Uh-huh.
There's no way
I'm not voting Rome tonight.
Let's just stick... Can we
please just stick to the plan?
There is no way I can pull off
a Kishan blindside
without Rome and Sol,
but they're openly adversaries.
And then
Teeny doesn't have a vote,
and she's really close
with Kishan.
So that's really not an option
to me.
- I know.
- Like, why?
- 'Cause Genevieve loves us.
- Yeah.
But Rome and Sol have now
just had this big fight,
almost to the point
that it's irreparable damage
that can't be undone.
So it is going to take a miracle
to get them to work together.
There's just no, no, no way.
Sol, I just want to say
that, like, I know that I
probably came across way wrong,
and, like, I just want you
to know that I'm...
I apologize
if I came off threatening
or whatever, you know,
you may think.
All right, I appreciate that.
- Okay. Okay.
- Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. It's a game.
- We need to get control.
- Right, but...
- We're not gonna have it.
- ...after, after...
- Yes, we will. I...
We're not gonna have it.
Could be
a million-dollar decision.
Sol's like, "I don't want
to work with Rome."
Rome's like, "It's a done deal.
Sol is going home tonight."
And what would be best
for my game would be to take
a stealth shot at Kishan
that he wouldn't see coming.
Is it bad that I'm excited?
It's gonna be a wild night.
The problem is, you have
to be in the majority,
you need numbers.
It is not a one-person game.
Genevieve doesn't get to pick.
But with so few votes,
and because the Steal a Vote
advantage exists,
anything could happen,
and it wouldn't take too much
to turn the tide.
All right.
So let's start by talking
about today's challenge.
Rome, I've never really seen
anything like today in the sense
that you got to the puzzle
first and never got
a single piece,
not one piece of the puzzle.
You know, we did great
in the first part
of the challenge today.
We were the first ones to get
to the puzzle, so I stepped up.
I wanted to, you know,
try my hand at it.
And, unfortunately,
I failed pretty miserably.
I was surprised
that you never wanted
a different perspective,
like to step back
or to look at it this way.
You just kept,
like a doctor taking the...
Maybe Kishan can give
a better analogy, but...
- Scalpel.
Like the scalpel, yeah.
Well, I don't even know
if doing it differently
would have changed anything,
in all honesty.
I truly feel like we're just
not that great at those specific
type of puzzles.
Okay, so you lost,
you're back here at Tribal.
So, Sol, if I dropped in
on Camp Lavo this afternoon,
what would I notice happening?
Chaos times ten is what
you would have walked into.
- Wow.
- Yeah.
Look, after the challenge,
Rome announces to me
that he has a Steal a Vote,
which shocked the hell
out of me.
And he basically said,
"Since you're on the bottom,
you and I can work together.
"Uh, the only way
I'll do that, though,
is if you give me
your Shot in the Dark."
Listen, it's not like
he didn't write my name down
last Tribal Council. He did.
So I told him, "The only way
that I would trust you
"to work with you is if you
give me your Shot in the Dark.
"But if you don't,
"then I'm gonna use
my Steal a Vote on you,
"and you're not gonna be able
to play your Shot in the Dark,
and you're gonna
be going home tonight."
Sol, given the fact
that you did vote for Rome,
that's not
that unusual a request.
It's kind of smart,
but at the same time, for me,
the way he went about it,
that's the key.
I didn't appreciate it, and so
I said,
"Are you threatening me, dude?"
- Uh, what did you say?
- I said, "No.
- it's an ultimatum,
not a threat."
- Right.
And so, for me, it sounds
like a threat, so I said,
"No, I'm not doing it."
And, Rome, your threat about
- stealing his vote is...
- Ultimatum, Jeff.
- The ultimatum
about stealing his vote is
that you have
to have a vote in order
to play the Shot in the Dark.
Precisely. And I just want
to say, Jeff, I, in the moment,
thought that that was
the right thing to do,
but the way that I did it and
the way that I approached Sol
was just not respectful.
Everyone that knows me
in real life knows
I'm a super genuine person.
So I went to him today,
and I apologized,
and I think
that he does understand
that that's...
that's just not who I am.
Kishan,
what's your take on this?
Because
when there's only five of you,
it doesn't take much
to vote somebody out.
An argument can do it.
You know, we're spending
24 hours a day with each other.
I think
when you're so deprived of food,
you can't sleep at night,
there are parts
of people's personalities
that are gonna come out
that bother you, that irk you.
But I think if you let
an argument guide your vote,
that's letting emotions get
to you.
I think
when you're playing this game,
you have to be more strategic
than that.
-Teeny,
how about for you?
- From my vantage point
as somebody who wasn't involved
in the fight
and also from my vantage point
as someone
who did lose their vote
on a journey today,
all I could really do
is put trust
in the people that I had
worked with last Tribal Council
and hope that it goes well.
Genevieve,
what do you make about this?
Because it sounds like
there could be two people
that aren't voting.
Teeny lost her vote,
Rome is threatening
to steal somebody else's vote.
That means
it could be four total votes,
but just three people.
Yeah. It means...
those three people
have a lot of power.
And you better hope those three
people are working with you
and have your back, because
they're gonna rule the day
today.
Jeff, I don't think
at the end of the day
it changes much
because it comes down to trust.
You trust the conversations
you had.
You trust a plan
that you've set forward.
It doesn't matter
because you trust
- what the plan is in place.
-So, Sol,
that can't make you feel great.
Nope. Not great at all, and, um,
I'm just begging Rome,
bro, maybe not steal my vote?
I do have
my Shot in the Dark here.
If my vote is not gone,
I am playing it.
And, Rome, what's interesting
about this is,
that's a real person...
- Yeah.
- I am a very real person...
-...saying to you...
- ...in the flesh behind you.
- Yeah.
- ...that, "I'm already
in trouble, I think.
And now you're taking
the only protection I have,"
which is the only move to make
if you want to take out Sol.
But Sol's pleading with you,
"Give me a shot."
At the end of the day,
it's going
to be my decision whether or not
I, uh, I take this guy's vote
or not, and,
you know, I just got to trust
the people that I trust,
and the people that I don't
trust, I'm not gonna trust you,
and I'm going
to do everything I can
to get you out of this game.
Wow.
Ooh.
- Spooky, scary, right?
- Yeah.
Is that the kind of laugh
you give when you're watching
Survivor at home, Genevieve?
When I'm watching Tribal,
and it gets like this,
and you're like,
"Oh, my God. Ooh,
something's happening." Like...
So from all this chaos,
where do you sit right now as
we are moments away from voting?
So, chaos times ten can be great
as long as you're not in it.
But honestly,
if I'm wrong tonight,
it's over for me.
So I think that this vote is
critical to the future success
of my game.
All right, it is time to vote.
You know, Jeff, I, uh...
I trust the people
that I trust, like I said,
and I don't trust the people
that I don't trust.
So I got a Steal a Vote, and
I'm gonna be stealing
Kishan's vote tonight.
All right,
this is a Steal a Vote.
Rome, you are
taking Kishan's vote,
which means, Kishan,
you will not vote tonight.
Rome, when you go up,
you will vote twice.
All right, it is time to vote.
Genevieve, you're up.
I'm absolutely freaking out.
I'll go tally the votes.
If anybody has an advantage
or an idol,
and you want to play it,
now would be the time to do so.
All right, I'll read the votes.
First vote-- Kishan.
Kishan.
That's two votes-- Kishan.
Fourth person voted out
of Survivor 47-- Kishan.
That's three. That's enough.
Need to bring me your torch.
I love you, Kishan.
I love you.
You guys are amazing.
Good game.
Kishan, the tribe has spoken.
Time for you to go.
Good luck, y'alls.
- Thank you, man.
- Thanks, Kishan.
- Bye, Kishan.
Love you, brother.
Grab your torches.
Head back to camp.
Good night.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS
and TOYOTA.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
We've got a brand-new
Survivor twist.
Next time on Survivor...
Right.
That creates some fireworks.
What?!
I'm angry.
I want to crush
her Survivor dream,
and I want to smile
while it happens.
I got blindsided,
as simple as it can be.
Some people may have
caught wind of what I was doing,
which led to my downfall.
So, props to them.
I respect the move.
I respect what they did.
Had I wished I had made
final three? Of course.
Had I wished I won? Yes.
But I have no regrets.
That's the beauty of the game.
You never know what to expect,
and that's what makes it fun.